Guide to the Robin Morgan Papers, 1940s-2019 and undated, bulk 1970-2019 RL.00913
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession (2016-0176), 2012-2016
  - Women's Media Center Live (WMCL), 2012-2016
    - 2013
      - Episode 62, 2013-12-07 (Box 2)
      - Episode 63, 2013-12-14 (Box 2)
      - Episode 64, 2013-12-14 (Box 2)
    - 2014
      - Episode 65, 2014-01-11 (Box 2)
      - Episode 66, 2014-01-18 (Box 2)
      - Episode 67, 2014-01-25 (Box 2)
      - Episode 68, 2014-02-01 (Box 2)
      - Episode 69, 2014-02-08 (Box 2)
      - Episode 70, 2014-02-15 (Box 2)
      - Episode 71, 2014-02-22 (Box 2)
      - Episode 72, 2014-03-01 (Box 2)
      - Episode 73, 2014-03-08 (Box 2)
      - Episode 74, 2014-03-15 (Box 2)
      - Episode 75, 2014-03-22 (Box 2)
      - Episode 76, 2014-03-29 (Box 2)
      - Episode 77, 2014-04-05 (Box 2)
      - Episode 78, 2014-04-12 (Box 2)
      - Episode 79, 2014-04-19 (Box 2)
      - Episode 80, 2014-04-26 (Box 2)
      - Episode 81, 2014-05-03 (Box 2)
      - Episode 82, 2014-05-10 (Box 2)
      - Episode 83, 2014-05-17 (Box 2)
      - Episode 84, 2014-05-24 (Box 2)
      - Episode 85, 2014-05-31 (Box 2)
      - Episode 86, 2014-06-07 (Box 2)
      - Episode 87, 2014-06-14 (Box 2)
      - Episode 88, 2014-06-21 (Box 2)
      - Episode 89, 2014-06-28 (Box 2)
      - Episode 90, 2014-07-05 (Box 2)
      - Episode 91, 2014-07-12 (Box 2)
      - Episode 92, 2014-07-19 (Box 2)
      - Episode 93, 2014-07-26 (Box 2)
      - Episode 94, 2014-09-06 (Box 2)
      - Episode 95, 2014-09-13 (Box 2)
      - Episode 96, 2014-09-20 (Box 2)
      - Episode 97, 2014-09-27 (Box 2)
      - Episode 98, 2014-10-04 (Box 2)
      - Episode 99, 2014-10-11 (Box 2)
      - Episode 100, 2014-10-18 (Box 2)
      - Episode 101, 2014-10-25 (Box 2)
      - Episode 102, 2014-11-01 (Box 2)
      - Episode 103, 2014-11-08 (Box 2)
      - Episode 104, 2014-11-15 (Box 2)
      - Episode 105, 2014-11-22 (Box 2)
      - Episode 106, 2014-12-06 (Box 2)
      - Episode 107, 2014-12-13 (Box 2)
      - Episode 108, 2014-12-20 (Box 2)
      - The Status of Women in the U.S. Media 2014 (Box 3)
    - 2015
      - Episode 109, 2015-01-10 (Box 2)
      - Episode 110, 2015-01-17 (Box 2)
      - Episode 111, 2015-01-24 (Box 3)
      - Episode 112, 2015-01-31 (Box 3)
      - Episode 113, 2015-02-07 (Box 3)
      - Episode 114, 2015-02-14 (Box 3)
      - Episode 115, 2015-02-21 (Box 3)
      - Episode 116, 2015-02-28 (Box 3)
      - Episode 117, 2015-03-14 (Box 3)
      - Episode 118, 2015-03-21 (Box 3)
      - Episode 119, 2015-03-28 (Box 3)
      - Episode 120, 2015-04-04 (Box 3)
      - Episode 121, 2015-04-11 (Box 3)
      - Episode 122, 2015-04-18 (Box 3)
      - Episode 123, 2015-04-25 (Box 3)
      - Episode 124, 2015-05-02 (Box 3)
      - Episode 125, 2015-05-09 (Box 3)
      - Episode 126, 2015-05-23 (Box 3)
      - Episode 127, 2015-05-30 (Box 3)
      - Episode 128, 2015-06-06 (Box 3)
      - Episode 129, 2015-06-13 (Box 3)
      - Episode 130, 2015-06-20 (Box 3)
      - Episode 131, 2015-06-27 (Box 3)
      - Episode 132, 2015-07-04 (Box 3)
      - Episode 133, 2015-07-11 (Box 3)
      - Episode 134, 2015-07-18 (Box 3)
      - Episode 135, 2015-07-25 (Box 3)
      - Episode 136, 2015-09-12 (Box 3)
      - Episode 137, 2015-09-19 (Box 3)
      - Episode 138, 2015-09-26 (Box 3)
      - Episode 139, 2015-10-03 (Box 3)
      - Episode 140, 2015-10-10 (Box 3)
      - Episode 141, 2015-10-17 (Box 3)
      - Episode 142, 2015-10-24 (Box 3)
      - Episode 143, 2015-10-31 (Box 3)
      - Episode 144, 2015-11-07 (Box 3)
      - Episode 145, 2015-11-14 (Box 3)
      - Episode 146, 2015-11-21 (Box 3)
      - Episode 147, 2015-12-05 (Box 3)
      - Episode 148, 2015-12-12 (Box 3)
      - Episode 149, 2015-12-19 (Box 3)
        - The Status of Women in the U.S. Media 2015 (Box 3)
    - 2016
      - Episode 150, 2016-01-09 (Box 3)
      - Episode 151, 2016-01-16 (Box 3)
      - Episode 152, 2016-01-23 (Box 3)
      - Episode 153, 2016-01-30 (Box 3)
      - Episode 154, 2016-02-06 (Box 3)
      - Episode 155, 2016-02-13 (Box 3)
      - Episode 156, 2016-02-20 (Box 3)
      - Episode 157, 2016-02-27 (Box 3)
      - Episode 158, 2016-03-05 (Box 3)
      - Episode 159, 2016-03-12 (Box 3)
      - Episode 160, 2016-03-19 (Box 3)
      - Episode 161, 2016-03-26 (Box 3)
      - Episode 162, 2016-04-02 (Box 3)
      - Episode 163, 2016-04-16 (Box 3)
      - Episode 164, 2016-04-23 (Box 3)
      - Episode 165, 2016-04-30 (Box 3)
      - Episode 166, 2016-05-07 (Box 3)
      - Episode 167, 2016-05-14 (Box 3)
      - Episode 168, 2016-05-21 (Box 3)
      - Episode 169, 2016-05-21 (Box 3)
  - Professional, 2015
    - Ms. Magazine Spring 2015 Issue (Box 2)
    - Barnard College: 7th Annual Global Symposium, 2015-03 (Box 4)
    - Gender Research Institute at Dartmouth, 2015-05-01 (Box 4)
    - The World Summit: End Sexual Exploitation 2025, 2015-05-11-2015-05-12 (Box 4)
    - TED x Women Talk, 2015-05 (Box 4)
    - Women and Foreign Policy Conference, 2015-09 (Box 4)
    - Women's Media Center Correspondence, 2015 (Box 4)
    - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 4)
    - 2013 Women's Media Awards disks (Box 5)
    - Sisterhood is Global Institute disk, undated (Box 5)
    - Ms. Magazine Winter 2015 Issue (Box 5)
    - Women's Media Center (WMC) Gala, 2013 (Box 5)
    - Ms. Magazine Summer 2015 Issue (Box 5)
- Accession (2019-0145), 1981-2019; 7.5 Linear Feet
  Materials include Women's Media Center Live materials, writings by Morgan including articles and drafts of her books Dark Matter and Parallax; correspondence, lectures, and research and activist files.
  Women's Media Center materials are closed by donor request.
  - Women's Media Center Live (WMCL) Shows #170-211, 2016-2017 (Box 1)
  - WMCL Shows #212-257, 2017-2018 (Box 2)
  - WMCL Shows #258-279, 2018-2019 (Box 3)
  - WMCL Old Guest Lists, 2004-2019 (Box 3)
  - WMC Publication: The Status of Women of Color in the U.S. News Media, 2018 (Box 3)
  - WMC Board of Directors Meetings, 2017-2018 (Box 3)
  - Poem Drafts, 2010-2018 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, 2017 (Box 4)
  - Sisterhood is Global Institute Annual Report, 2016 (Box 4)
  - Jury Duty, 2017 (Box 4)
  - Italian Language Periodicals with Morgan Articles, 1999-2017 (Box 4)
  - Dark Matter Galleys, 2018 (Box 4)
  - Dark Matter Production, 2017-2018 (Box 4)
  - Dark Matter Final Manuscript, 2017-2018 (Box 4)
  - French Festival, 2017 (Box 4)
  - Publisher Correspondence, 1981-2017 (Box 4)
  - Lectures, 1988-2014 (Box 4)
  - Academic Correspondence, 2004 (Box 4)
  - Donor Direct Action, 2011-2013 (Box 4)
  - Adelaide Fest, 2019 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, 2018 (Box 4)
  - Ms. Magazine Production Materials and Correspondence, Winter 2016-Summer 2019 (Box 5)
  - Parallax: A Novel Manuscript, circa 2019 (Box 5)